A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Bronx Zoo - Legislation, 1962-1974 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - By-Laws, 1968-1971 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Clippings, 1972-1976 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Conservation Committee, 1969-1975 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Contributions (Miscellaneous) - A-Z, 1968-1971 (Box 259, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Contributions - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1971 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Employees, 1962-1970 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Finances, 1968-1975 (Box 260, Folder 1-2, Box 261)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Fund raising, 1975-1976 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Legal, 1969-1971 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Membership, 1969-1975 (Box 262, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Memoranda, 1968-1975 (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Minutes/Meetings (Box 262, Folder 4-5)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Annual Members Meeting, 1972-1976 (Box 263, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 263, Folder 3-7)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 (Box 263, Folder 8-10, Box 264, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - New York City - Parks Recreation and Cultural Affairs Administration, 1973-1975 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Osborn, Fairfield, 1966-1971 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Planning Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Printed Material, 1966-1976 (Box 264, Folder 6, Box 265, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1968-1976 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Addresses, 1966-1971 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Rockefeller University Institute of Research, on Animal Behavior, 1964-1970 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Staff, 1969-1976 (Box 266, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Whale Fund, 1968-1975 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - New York Zoological Society - Wildlife Survival Center, 1970-1972 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - North American Wildlife Foundation, 1962-1969 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Northern Plains Project, 1973-1976 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Open Space Action Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Orell, Bernard L., 1963-1967 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Palisades Nature Association, 1963-1970 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Richard M. Nixon, 1968-1969 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - A-Z (Box 267, Folder 3-4)
  - Conservation - Parks - American Institute of Park Executives, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Parks - Council for Parks and Playgrounds, Inc., 1963-1968 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Conference on State Parks, 1964-1974 (Box 268, Folder 1-4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Conference on State Parks - Constitution and By-Laws, 1966-1967 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - General, 1963-1976 (Box 269, Folder 3-4, Box 270, Folder 1-4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - A-M (Box 271, Folder 1-3)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - N-Z (Box 272, Folder 1-3)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Annual Report, Executive Directorship, Policy, Presidency, 1966-1971 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Board of Trustees, 1966-1973 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Booz, Allen, and Hamilton, Inc., 1965 (Box 273, Folder 2-3, Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Budget, 1966-1971 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Committees, 1967-1970 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Conferences, 1966-1977 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Contributions, 1966-1971 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Constitution and By-Laws, 1965-1968 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Finances, 1966-1974 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Fund Raising, 1966-1971 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Memoranda, 1966-1971 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - History, 1964-1970 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Administrative Board, 1965-1967 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Board of Trustees, 1965-1976 1966 May 21 (Box 276, Folder 3-4, Box 277, Folder 1-3, Box 278, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Congress for Recreation and Parks, 1966 October (Box 278, Folder 3-4, Box 279, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Austin, Texas, 1967 April 14-15 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Executive Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 279, Folder 3, Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - National Budget and Consultation Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Park Manual, 1965-1967 (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - "Parks and Recreation", 1966-1971 (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Personnel, 1966-1971 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    Restricted - Personnel material
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Printed Material, 1971-1974 (Box 281, Folder 1-2, Box 282)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Projects, 1966-1970 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Public Affairs, 1965-1970 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Publication Proposal, 1974 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Reports, 1964-1969 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1965-1969 (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Rosenberg, Anna M. Associates, 1966-1967 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - U.S.G. Department of the Treasury - IRS, 1966 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Smith, J. Austin, 1966-1970 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Wirth, Conrad L., 1966-1970 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Parks - Park Council, 1963-1971 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Parks - Tumucumaque National Park, 1967-1971 (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Parks - Tanzania National Parks, 1962-1970 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Parks - Virgin Islands International Park, 1958-1965 (Box 285, Folder 2-3, Box 286, Folder 1-3)
  - Conservation - Puerto Rico, 1973 (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - General, 1967 (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - American Bar Association, 1968 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Atomic Energy Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Atomic Industrial Forum, 1966-1968 (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Atomic Power Plans, 1966-1968 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Bechtel Corporation, 1967-1968 (Box 287, Folder 2-3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Cable Television, 1967-1968 (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - California Public Utilities Commission, 1967 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - California State-Wide Undergrounding Conference, 1967 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Central Hudson Gas & Electric, 1967-1968 (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Citizens Advisory Committee on Recreation & Natural Beauty, 1966-1968 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Cluster Development, 1968 August 23 (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Con Edison, 1967-1968 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Congress - Legislation, 1967-1968 (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Cornwall Project, 1965-1968 (Box 288, Folder 5-6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Department of Housing & Urban Develop. - FHA, 1965 (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Department of the Interior, 1967 (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Distribution Lines, 1965-1968 (Box 288, Folder 9)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Henry Dreyfuss, 1966 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Economics, 1966-1968 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Edison Electric Institute, 1967-1969 (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Electric Car, 1967-1968 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - Electric Power Reliability Act, 1967 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Electric Research Council, 1966-1968 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Electric Utility Industry Task Force on Environment (Box 290, Folder 1-4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Environment, 1966-1967 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Environment Policy & Organization Commission, 1965-1968 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Federal Power Commission (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Flags, 1968 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - High Mountain Sheep Project, 1967-1968 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Hudson Highlands State Park, 1967 (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1966-1967 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - IBEC/NPA Luncheon, 1968 April 11 (Box 291, Folder 8-16, Box 292, Folder 1-4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Indiana Electric Association, 1967 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - International Federation of Landscape Architecture, 1968 (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Inter-venors, 1967 (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Landscape - Architects, 1968 (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Michigan Public Service Commission, 1968 (Box 292, Folder 9)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - National Association of Railroad & Utilities Commissioners, 1967 (Box 292, Folder 10)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - National Planning Association, 1968 (Box 292, Folder 11)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - New York State Park Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 292, Folder 12)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Pacific Coast Electrical Association, 1968 (Box 292, Folder 13)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Phillips, Walter, 1966-1968 (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Pilot City Study, undated (Box 293, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - P.I.P. - Public Information Program, 1967-1968 (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Poles (Electric Transmission) - Wood, 1967-1968 (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Pollution, 1966-1967 (Box 293, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Public Land Law Review Commission, 1966-1967 (Box 293, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Public Utility Commission - URD - Regulations, 1967 (Box 293, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - President's Council on Recreation & Natural Beauty, 1968 (Box 293, Folder 8)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Presidential Candidates - Platform, 1968 (Box 293, Folder 8A)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Public Opinion Polls, 1967 (Box 293, Folder 9)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Redwood National Park, 1967 (Box 293, Folder 10)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Roads, 1967 (Box 293, Folder 11)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Laurance S. Rockefeller Interview - Electrical World Magazine Rural Co-ops, 1968 (Box 293, Folder 12)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Rural Coops (Box 293, Folder 13)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Sillin, Lelan F., 1967-1968 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Staff Executive Committee of E.U.I.T.F. on Environment, 1967-1968 (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - Task Force - Electric Utility Industry Task Force on Environment - Meeting, NYC, 1967 March 15 (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Meeting, San Francisco, 1967 June 16 (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Meeting, Chicago, 1967 October 19 (Box 294, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Meeting, Phoenix, 1968 February 15 (Box 294, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Meeting - New York City, 1968 March 12 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Meeting - New York City (cancelled), 1968 April 25 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Meeting - New York City (cancelled), 1968 May 21 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Meeting - New York City, 1968 June 20 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Members, 1967-1968 (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Outlines, 1968 (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Task Force Report Files (Box 296, Folder 1-6, Box 297, Folder 1-5, Box 298, Folder 1-3)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Telephone, 1968 (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Thermal Pollution, 1968 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Transmission Lines, 1967 (Box 298, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Undergrounding Equipment, 1967 (Box 298, Folder 7)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Undergrounding Projects, 1966-1968 (Box 298, Folder 8)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Urban Development Corporation, 1968 (Box 298, Folder 9)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Vermont Project, 1967 (Box 298, Folder 10)
  - Conservation - Harry Rand - Water Quality, 1968 (Box 298, Folder 11)
  - Conservation - Recreation - A-C, 1961-1976 (Box 298, Folder 12)
  - Conservation - Recreation - D-N, 1961-1976 (Box 299, Folder 1-3)
  - Conservation - Recreation - O-Z (Box 300, Folder 1-4)
  - Conservation - Recreation - Caribbean Hotel Association, 1975 (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Recreation - National Recreation Association, 1962-1965 (Box 300, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Recreation - National Recreation Association - Printed Material (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Recreation - U.S. Ski Educational Foundation Inc., 1966-1976 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Recreation - Resources for the Future - Board of Directors, 1965-1973 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Recreation - Resources for the Future, 1962-1976 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Recreation - Resources for the Future - Grants, 1962-1968 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Recreation - Resources for the Future - Minutes/Meetings, 1964-1974 (Box 302, Folder 2, Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Recreation - Resources for the Future - Resources in America's Future, 1963 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Recreation - Resources for the Future - Printed Material, 1964-1976 (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - American Conservation Association - General Correspondence (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - American Conservation Association - Contributions, 1966-1976 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - American Conservation Association - Finances, 1962-1976 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - American Conservation Association - Minutes/Meetings, 1962-1970 (Box 304, Folder 2-3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Jackson Hole Preserve, 1961-1965 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Jackson Hole Preserve - Contributions, 1962-1969 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Jackson Hole Preserve - Finances, 1962-1971 (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Jackson Hole Preserve - Minutes/Meetings, 1962-1972 (Box 305, Folder 4, Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Jackson Hole Preserve - Brochure (Box 306, Folder 2-3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Jackson Hole Preserve - Grand Teton Lodge Company (Box 308, Folder 1-4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Caneel Bay, 1961-1971 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Caneel Bay - Finances, 1967-1973 (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Caneel Bay - Minutes/Meetings, 1962-1969 (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Caneel Bay - Public Affairs (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1963-1976 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Holt Bodinson, 1968-1970 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Henry Diamond, 1964-1970 (Box 309, Folder 3-4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Carl Gustafson, 1959-1963 (Box 310, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Fred Smith, 1963-1975 (Box 310, Folder 3-4, Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Romney, Henry, 1960-1961 (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Conrad Wirth, 1964-1976 (Box 311, Folder 3-4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Save the Redwoods League - Rockefeller Redwood Forest - Clippings, 1963-1965 (Box 311, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Save the Redwoods League - Rockefeller Redwood Forest, 1962-1971 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1975-1976 (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Sierra Club, 1959-1971 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - A-Z, 1964-1972 (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - General, 1956-1963 (Box 313, Folder 1-3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Addresses - A-Z, 1965-1972 (Box 313, Folder 4-5, Box 314, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Addresses - Financial Executive's Institute - America is a Growing Country, 1971 (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Addresses - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, 1969-1971 (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Albright Testimonial Dinner, 1959 December 4 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Albright Testimonial Dinner - Finances, 1959-1960 (Box 315, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Boone and Crocket Club, 1956-1964 (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Dinosaur National Park, 1959-1963 (Box 316, Folder 1-4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Indiana Dunes, 1958-1963 (Box 316, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Edward Mallinckrodt, Jr., 1958-1964 (Box 317, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Natural Resources Position Papers, 1960-1963 (Box 317, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - New York State Advisory Committee to Conservation Commissioner, 1956-1965 (Box 317, Folder 4, Box 318, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - New York State (Temporary) Commission for the Preservation and Protection of Historic Sites, 1956-1958 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - New York State Northway, 1959 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Rayonier and Forest Practices material, 1959-1960 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Printed Material, 1970 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Rockefeller Center Luncheon Club, 1964 (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - General Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Save Our Shoreline, 1959-1960 (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Federal Power Commission Environmental Task Force, 1970-1971 (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Rockefeller Family Interests - Fred Smith - Wilderness Bill, 1961-1972 (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc., 1965-1976 (Box 320, Folder 1-2)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Contributions, 1972-1973 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Finances, 1976-1977 (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - A-Z (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Contract Agreements (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Contributions (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Finances (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Fund Raising (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Conservation - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Fundraising - A-Z (Box 322, Folder 1-5)